surveys4income.com 2015-05-13

# Paid Surveys- Earn Real Income From Home

Privacy Policy

Survey4Income.com takes your privacy seriously, and has created this Privacy Policy in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to online privacy. Keep reading to learn more about our information gathering and dissemination practices, and our use of personally identifiable information. 

IP Addresses

We may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our site or web server, and for the general administration of our website. Your IP address, should you decide to register and/or create a Survey4Income account, is also used to help prevent you from creating duplicate accounts.

Cookies

Upon your first visit to this web site, a "cookie" is sent to your computer. A cookie is a tiny file that identifies you as a unique user. It stores personal preferences and user data, however, in no way does this tell us who you are. Survey4Income.com has two primary uses for its cookies.

First, we use cookies to track special offers and promotions that may be presented to you as you navigate our website. This is done so that you are not presented with the same special offers and/or promotions over and over, or after you have indicated you are not interested.

Secondly, we use cookies as part of our authentication system when you login to your account. If you select the "remember me" option when logging in, our site will set a cookie so that you do not have to login again the next time you visit Survey4Income.com.

While both of these activities depend on the use of a "cookie," visitors to this site always have the option of disabling cookies in their web browser. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or indicate when a cookie is being sent.

Information Gathering

This web site collects online contact information in various ways, including inquiry forms, registration forms, surveys, and contests. The information collected may be used to send the user information about our company, or to get in touch with the user when necessary.

Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the opt-out/modify section below.

Information Dissemination

We may use the personal information that you supply to us and we may work with other third party businesses to bring selected retail opportunities to our members via email. These businesses may include providers of direct marketing services and applications, including lookup and reference, data enhancement, suppression and validation and email marketing.

Links to Other Sites

Survey4Income.com expects its partners, advertisers and affiliates to respect the privacy of our users. Be aware, however, that third parties, including our partners, advertisers, affiliates and other content providers accessible through our site, may have their own privacy and data collection policies and practices. For example, during your visit to our site you may link to, or view as part of a frame of content that is actually created or hosted by a third party.

Also, via our site you may be introduced to, or be able to access, information, Web sites, features, contests or sweepstakes offered by other parties. Survey4Income.com is not responsible for the actions or policies of such third parties. You should check the applicable privacy policies of those third parties when providing information on a feature or page operated by a third party.

Please be aware that if you voluntarily disclose Personally Identifiable Information on message boards or in chat areas, that information can be viewed publicly and can be collected and used by third parties without our knowledge and may result in unsolicited messages from other individuals or third parties. Such activities are beyond the control of Survey4Income.com and this policy.

Children Under 13

Survey4Income.com does not knowingly collect or solicit Personally Identifiable Information from or about children under 13 except as permitted by law. If we discover we have received any information from a child under 13 in violation of this policy, we will delete that information immediately. If you believe Survey4Income.com has any information from or about anyone under 13, please contact us.

Security

This web site has security measures in place to protect against loss, misuse and/or alteration of the information that you provide. Furthermore, we have taken every precaution technically possible to prevent any unauthorized access to the contents of this web server.

Opt-Out/Modify

Survey4Income.com provides every user with the opportunity to opt-out of receiving future communications from us, change and modify information previously provided, or remove their information from our databases altogether. You may do so in any of the following ways:

1\. Email: support@Survey4Income.com  
2\. Website: http://www.Survey4Income.com

Earnings Disclaimer

Surveys4Income makes every effort to provide accurate and complete information on paid surveys, focus groups, and each of the ways to make money online. We cannot guarantee any income because the amount of money that can be made varies based on a number of factors including but not limited to geographical location, gender, age, time available and interests. Examples of earnings are used purely to express the potential of this industry, we do not promise or guarantee any earnings. Surveys4Income.com provides no warranty, expressed or implied, as to the accuracy, reliability or completeness of the furnished data.

Contacting Survey4Income.com

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this web site, or your dealings with this web site, please contact us.

Policy Changes

Survey4Income reserves the right to change this privacy policy at any time.

(C)Copyright 2007-2099 [Surveys4Income.com](http://www.surveys4income.com/),Helen Shilton & Associates
